[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
-[Julio] Who killed Sanggano?!
-[goon] It was Diego Torillo.
[Julio] So, a man with a clean conscience
can actually kill.
[Emilia] Arnaldo, my son!
[Arnaldo] I have lots
of questions about Lily.
-And if you can answer--
-[Julio] You'll come back.
I will answer all your questions,
but you have to come back home.
[Mercedes] Deliver the documents
to Red Dragon
to the address written below
and not to the original one,
so the enemy cannot track them.
As you wish.
Madam, here are your files.
-[Lily in Chinese] Hello, Mercedes.
-You?!
[Lily] Yes, Mercedes, it's me.
I always make sure to know
my enemies well,
so that I can camouflage as the enemy.
[Helena] Mercedes, I'll use
Diego Torillo against Julio.
This is the perfect venue
to get revenge on Lily Cruz.
I will join your group not as a lackey,
but as Red Dragon's ally.
Welcome to the organization
as Red Dragon's ally.
[Lily] What's going on here?
Surrender Diego Torillo to me.
Diego Torillo is not here!
[Julio] This is crazy! Search the place!
-[gunshots]
-[Lily] Go ahead, Julio!
I won't hesitate to blow
a hole in your skull!
-[Julio] No!
-[Lily] Get out!
Leave my property!
Okay, okay. I'm leaving.
-Now!
-[Julio] Yes! Yes, now. Okay.
Back up, fools!
She's crazy! She's mad!
I'm leaving!
Never thought this woman
could be so crazy!
[tense music swelling]
[Emilia] Hi, Papa!
So, did your minions find Diego Torillo?
They're a bunch of slowpokes.
They're nothing compared
to the men of Sanggano.
That's one thing
that I despise about Diego.
He took out one of my best men.
Hmm…
What if I tell you, Papa,
that I know where Diego is?
[scoffs]
And you expect me to believe you, right?
Hmm…
You should believe me.
But I cannot understand it for you,
so I won't tell you anything.
So, get back to work, Papa.
Oh, you can't go back to work
because you're not yet in the position.
So, technically, you have no work to do.
[chuckling]
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Laugh your head off. Laugh all you want.
-But I bet you all my assets.
-Wow.
I'll be restored as the governor
of Poblacion Ardiente.
And, when I return, do you know what my
first legislation will be?
I'll have you banned in this town!
Wow, you're so harsh, Papa!
[sighs]
Look, Papa! Look! Watch!
The campaign period had just started.
When Diego Torillo's volunteers gathered,
suddenly, we were attacked
Julio Ardiente's men.
I was shot by Julio Ardiente!
That man tried to kill me!
[gunshots]
-[gunshots]
-[Camia grunting]
[gunshots]
He cheated during the elections!
He has no right to be reinstated
as the governor of this town!
I am pleading to the witnesses
of the incident,
don't be afraid.
Let us unite
to prevent Julio Ardiente's
return to power!
[woman] Is that true?
Actually, I was there when it happened.
I witnessed how the congressman
shot Miss Camia.
Then, why won't you testify?
There are two possible scenarios
if I do that.
Bite the bullet or get paid off.
I'm lucky if they pay me.
But if not, I'd rather shut up.
I'm scared of the Ardientes.
My family might get hurt too.
Of course, those witnesses are afraid.
The Ardientes may not be
the most powerful,
but they're the richest.
And with the return of Emilia's mom,
Helena Montoya, who's filthy rich,
their fortune doubles!
-That family is too much.
-They're crooked.
Yeah, right.
Why do they gossip about grandpa
like he's an evil person?
[reporter] Thank you, Camia Cruz.
Camia Cruz?
Camia Cruz? The mother of Lily Cruz?
[groaning]
[tense music swelling]
[breathing heavily]
But some news says
that your claim is just a scam
to smear the impending return
of Congressman Julio Ardiente as governor.
That's not true!
Let's take a look at this report.
My name is Liza Paras, a teacher.
I was also a volunteer for Diego Torillo
during the last election.
I refute Camia's claims.
Congressman Julio Ardiente
wasn't there that day.
So, it's impossible for him
to have shot Camia.
[Camia] Teacher Liza, that's not true!
You are lying! You were there!
You liar!
[reporter] Will this development help
in the pending appeal of Julio Ardiente
to be reinstated as the governor
of Poblacion Ardiente?
Stay tuned.
Poblacion Ardiente.
Your handsome governor is back!
[laughing and clapping]
How do you like that?
Now, what can you say about it,
little brat?
I'm not gonna comment now, Papa.
I'll cross that bridge when I get there.
I hope the bridge burns.
[door closes]
Congratulations, Mercedes.
You closed the deal with Diego Torillo.
So, I guess, I've redeemed myself
in your eyes, Madam.
[scoffs] Not so fast.
Lily Cruz is still out there
with evidence against us.
What about the vault? Is it secure enough?
But of cour--
[tense music playing]
[grunts loudly]
Mercedes?!
[exhales] Yes, Madam.
Good.
[line ringing]
Hello, Mr. Larson.
I'm calling about Red Dragon's vault.
[suspenseful music]
[elevator bell dings]
Helena Montoya's account, please.
Key, please.
Show her through. Thank you.
[line ringing]
Security, she's here.
[suspenseful music continues]
[alarm blaring]
[door opens]
Your key doesn't work!
Maybe that's what triggered the alarm!
What kind of service is this?!
I'm very sorry, Madam.
This is your faulty key!
I don't need it anymore!
[action music playing]
[elevator bell dings]
[dings]
Thank you.
-Mom.
-Lily.
I heard about what happened
during the interview.
Don't worry, that has no basis in court.
[exhales]
I hope so.
Do you have the documents?
I have bank statements, files,
and other transactions,
but what I need is the list
of Red Dragon's clients.
That's what I need the most.
[Mercedes] What do you mean,
it won't open?!
It might be the wrong key.
This is the correct key.
Unless Lily Cruz might have replaced it.
[alarm blares]
Where is your CCTV?!
I need to know what's been going on here.
Give me an update the minute
you open this vault.
Do you understand?!
And Red Dragon must never
find out about this!
Am I making myself clear?!
[Vanessa] So, Diego Torillo…
You're officially part of our group.
Maybe you should get to know us better.
[Romulo clears throat]
Mercedes told me to keep an eye on you,
so behave yourself!
You can't do
extracurricular activities here.
I'm here for my mission.
What mission?
To bring down the Ardientes.
If you say so,
I'll take your word on that.
I hope Red Dragon was right
to recruit you.
-[phone ringing]
-Stay right there.
-We'll have your training later.
-[phone ringing]
Yes, Mr. Black?
The shipment is ready.
[tense music playing]
When should we make the barter?
Okay, sure.
What are you looking at?
Do you have a problem?
Are you curious about what I'm doing?
Maybe you're a spy!
I'm observing how I'm going
to replace you.
-What a piece of--
-Go ahead.
I'm not a lackey like you.
I'm an ally of Red Dragon.
Let us see how she'll react
if you dare touch me.
[man] Boss! Idol! You're the man!
Is it true? You're going to live here?
I thought your brother's wife
had you on a leash.
Now what? Let's go back to business!
Both of you, shut up.
I'm not in the mood to fool around.
[tense music]
Boss, we've got company!
[Fabian] Well, look at this,
the fake Jaguar.
[Raul] I'm unarmed.
Can we talk?
Lower your guns!
Are you two deaf? Put down your guns!
Leave us!
Why did you come here?
I just want to thank you…
for what you did for me and Diego Torillo.
You helped us.
Why did you do that?
It's over now. You may leave.
Diego Torillo is here
in Red Dragon's lair.
I came to ask for a favor.
Please look after the kid.
What is Diego Torillo to you?
We don't have the time for that story.
Just look after the kid
because he's important to me.
Diego Torillo is a good kid.
You can count on me.
Thank you.
Thanks. And even though I know
that this is not my mask,
and I stole it from you,
you still helped us.
Now, to make it up to you
and end this conversation…
[Damian] Stop.
Let's use these masks
to protect the people we love…
and in our fight against the Ardientes.
Jaguar.
Thank you.
[action music playing]
[action music continues]
They were right. You really are fast.
-Because I'm not all talk.
-Is that so?
[grunts]
[thumping]
[Vanessa] Boss? Boss?
Boss?
[Romulo coughing]
Where's Diego?
Diego!
Put that down!
[Diego] My apologies.
I thought it was mine.
-[grunts]
-[coughs]
The next time you touch my things,
you'll get even worse.
I don't care if you're the apple
of Red Dragon's eye
because I'll beat you up so bad!
No one will recognize your pretty face!
Speak up!
You think highly of yourself!
[Diego groaning]
[Jaguar] Romulo!
Jaguar!
[Jaguar] We're all on the same side.
We shouldn't be killing each other!
Since when did you become a babysitter?!
Let go of Diego!
[Diego gags and coughs]
-You better teach this kid!
-[Diego coughing]
He's touching my stuff!
[Diego breathing heavily]
[Jaguar] Inform me the next time
Romulo bothers you.
You are the other Jaguar.
Who are you?
I am the original.
I don't need your help.
[Jaguar] That's what you think.
You turned your back
on a lot of people to get here.
You're all alone. You need some support.
I can take care of myself.
[tense music]
[gunshot]
-[gunshot]
-[gasps]
[panting]
[tense music continues]
[Jepoy] Arnaldo, let's eat.
Anna made you some food.
You haven't eaten all day.
Let's eat together.
Arnaldo! Stop!
-What are you doing?!
-Let go of me!
No, no, no! Have you gone mad?!
Let me die! Please!
Hold on! This is not the way!
-What's the matter?!
-I don't know!
Then, what's the right way?!
Nothing makes sense!
I can't take it anymore!
What's the matter with you?!
-I don't know! I give up!
-If I didn't show up in time…
-I give up!
-…you'd be dead by now.
I give up! I don't know!
-What's wrong, Arnaldo?!
-I don't know!
I don't know, Jepoy!
Come on. What's the matter?
Lily… Lily.
Take me to Lily.
She can answer my questions.
I need to talk to her.
Bring me to Lily.
Jepoy, bring me to Lily. [whimpering]
Come on! Bring me to Lily!
Take me to Lily!
Please! I'm begging you!
She's the only one who can help me.
It's killing me. I don't know what to do.
-[Arnaldo] Lily!
-[Jepoy] Arnaldo.
-Lily!
-[Jepoy] Calm down, Arnaldo!
-She won't talk to you.
-[Arnaldo] Lily!
Lily, come out!
Get your act together. Cool down.
[Arnaldo] Jepoy, I just want
to talk to her.
[tense music]
Ivy.
-[chuckles] Ivy.
-It's Lily.
Lily Cruz.
-That's my name.
-No, it's Ivy Aguas.
-It's Lily Cruz!
-Your name is Ivy Aguas!
I know because I've seen lots
of videos and photos of you.
There's even a news article
about a wedding.
Our wedding.
Our wedding that didn't push through.
Now, I want to know what happened.
Tell me what happened! What is the truth?!
What is the real truth?!
Tell me!
I'm not sure if the truth
would sit well with you.
But I think, Arnaldo,
it would be best if you don't know
-the whole story.
-No, I need to know, Lily!
-[Jepoy] Stop it, Arnaldo!
-[Arnaldo] Let me through!
Let me through! Ivy! Ivy! Ivy!
-[Jepoy] Wait, stop it.
-Ivy.
I just want to talk to her, Jepoy!
Ivy.
I don't know if I should
call you Ivy or Lily,
but I know for sure that I like you.
I've liked you
since the first time I saw you.
And then I discovered
our supposed marriage.
Can you blame me for asking questions?
Could you blame me?
Tell me the reason why you leave me.
[somber music playing]
Please answer me. I'm begging you.
You killed my Nanny Carlotta.
[tense music playing]
You're a murderer, Arnaldo!
You wanted the truth?!
That's the whole truth!
Now, you may leave my house!
[tense music intensifies]
[thumping]
[Lily] I know you want to be alone.
I'm sorry, I can't give you that.
I don't want to leave you.
That's why I'm here.
Forgive me.
["Nanghihinayang"
by Angeline Quinto playing]
[Lily] I won't let you turn
into a criminal!
There's no place for justice
here in Ardiente!
-I will kill them.
-[Lily] Diego!
[Jepoy] Diego!
Sanggano was found dead.
Information says that Diego
was the one who killed him.
I spoke with Diego earlier.
He said he wasn't ready to come back.
["Nanghihinayang" continues playing]
[Diego] I'll make sure
that your plans will succeed.
Even if it costs my life,
I won't let anything bad happen to you.
[Lily] Diego,
thank you for keeping your promise…
that you'd help me succeed.
I hope you'll be with me
until the very end.
["Nanghihinayang" continues playing]
[song fading]
[Arnaldo screaming]
I can't take it anymore!
[mumbling] Give me back my memories!
Are you punishing me?! Are you?! Huh?!
Give me back my memories.
Give them back.
[sobbing]
[Magbanua] Diego!
Diego Torillo.
I can't believe you are here all along.
Oh, that's right, you don't know me.
If you didn't kill Sanggano,
I wouldn't be here.
Thank you.
-Bring him in.
-[goon] Let's go!
[men grunting]
[goon] Hey! Stand up!
Come on! Stand up!
Stay still!
[grunting]
[grunts]
[thumps]
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[gagging]
[Magbanua coughs]
[exhales]
This one is yours.
[Helena] Mercedes.
Yes, Madam?
Bring me Diego Torillo.
[Helena] No, wait.
-Julio Ardiente attacked, right?
-Yes.
But nothing we can't handle.
The war has begun.
Tell Diego Torillo to wait.
I'm going somewhere. Get the car ready.
What happened?
You allowed a bunch of females
to beat your men to a pulp?!
Get out of here! Get lost! Get out!
Damn!
[door closes]
[sighs]
I know why you recruited
Diego Torillo, Helena.
You know that I will get mad and furious!
No matter.
Even if you and all my enemies
band together,
you are not going to shake me down.
Not the great Julio Ardiente!
Watch out.
[sighs deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
You all right?
Julio Ardiente is still after you.
The violence won't stop,
no matter whose camp you join.
It could be worse for you
now that you sided with Red Dragon.
Or maybe you have other motives?
Well, hello, "frenemy."
[scoffs]
-You're back.
-Yes, I feel safer now.
I made sure that my enemies
have something to worry about.
But you know what?
There's just one glitch.
Your underlings won't leave
my new apprentice.
Diego Torillo.
This is all your doing.
It's like you're taunting me.
You know that I am hunting that kid…
for killing my best henchman.
And just to annoy me…
you took him in like a son.
Well, not everything is about you, is it?
[chuckling]
There you are greatly mistaken.
Because everything is about me
in this town.
And the next time you spite me,
I'll turn your minions' heads
into bowling balls.
Julio, please stop making declarations
that you can't back up with power.
Real power, that apparently
you don't have right now.
[laughing]
Well, enjoy your supposed
temporary power while it lasts.
Because I won't allow you
to play the queen in my own territory.
And I'm going to make sure
that you kneel and beg
by the time I return as governor!
I'm telling you,
no woman has picked a fight
with me and won.
You're just a woman, Helena.
And as desirable as you are,
you won't win against me.
You're just a woman like Lily Cruz,
and like your daughter Emilia,
who's crazy like you.
Well, we'll see about that.
I'll get you yet.
[Helena scoffs]
It's finally nice to meet you
face to face.
Sit.
You know why you're here.
And you know why I'm here.
That worked quite well for you, didn't it?
You're alive because of my dragon ladies.
And I already spoke with Julio.
I told him to stop hunting you.
But that man is so delusional.
[upbeat music playing]
What's that for?
You want me to kill Julio?
[chuckles] You know what?
That was my first choice.
But then I thought…
you need a test run.
I heard…
you and Lily are a thing.
-We're over now.
-Really?
Cheers!
[clink]
[Lily] I learned my lesson, Attorney.
I need to file a lawsuit
that will bring Red Dragon down.
That's why I targeted her bank accounts…
to cripple her once the truth comes out.
But I need her list of clients
to further cripple her organization.
[Camia] But, Lily…
how are you going to get that list?
Remember, Mercedes
and Red Dragon had marked you
for infiltrating the organization.
That's right, Aunt Camia.
We are all marked.
That's why we can't move freely.
Maybe that is the reason
why Red Dragon took Diego in.
[Camia] What?!
Diego is now working for Red Dragon?
Yes.
Intel says that Julio Ardiente
attacked Diego,
but Red Dragon's minions
came to rescue him.
I can see two possible scenarios here.
First…
Red Dragon will use Diego
against you, Lily.
And second, she could use Diego
against Julio Ardiente.
Please sit down.
We've got different ideologies.
Well, you know what? You're right.
Immediately break free
when you feel that you are
being used and abused.
Don't be like me and Julio
who had a child.
[laughing]
For your first job as my ally…
I want you to kill Lily Cruz.
[tense music playing]
[Camia] Diego? Lily!
Have you heard anything from him?
In order to win against Red Dragon,
we need to maintain our focus.
We can't waste our time
on things like that.
I need to get that list.
And I have a plan.
My gift for you. I made it myself.
It's made of African diamonds.
Come on, try it. It's so beautiful on you.
I call it "Princess Emilia."
All right.
I'm sorry for not involving you
in the group's operations.
But I just wanted to protect
you, my baby girl, my princess.
Mama, I used to be a politician,
a governor.
I don't need this tiara.
What I want is to be part
of your organization.
All right.
I will make you my right-hand man,
along with Mercedes.
But, Mama…
For your first project,
I want you to take care
of the big, big comeback
of Helena Montoya,
for the anniversary of my organization.
Can you take care of that
for me, baby girl?
-Okay, Mama, I'll do it.
-[Helena giggles]
Come on, put it on.
It looks perfect on you.
-My princess.
-[chuckles]
[foreboding music playing]
[tense music playing]
Diego.
[romantic music playing]
I thought you'd never see me again.
I'm sorry for all I've said
and done to you.
I know you are just concerned about me.
I don't want to lose you.
I'll never leave.
I'll never leave you, Diego.
Like I said, everything you did,
I understand it all.
I feel your sentiments.
Diego…
I can never be mad at you.
Never.
I waited every single day…
because I knew…
I knew that you'd come back.
-Forgive me, Lily.
-[sniffles]
Please forgive me. Please forgive me.
There's something you should know.
I've infiltrated the lair of Red Dragon.
I've gained access to everything.
Just tell me what you need.
Diego, I need a list
of Red Dragon's clients.
Once I get that,
I can stop her entire operations.
The blue book.
-Diego.
-Here's the blue book.
It contains the list
of Red Dragon's clients.
What's your plan?
I'll have her lair raided.
Do not return there.
Lily.
[suspenseful music]
Listen to me, Diego.
If you return there without my head,
they'll kill you instead.
Diego, please.
Don't worry, Lily. I'll be fine.
What's important is we take down
Red Dragon and the Ardientes!
-I promise you, I'll be fine.
-Diego, please.
-Diego.
-I have to go.
Diego!
Diego.
[sighs]
[dramatic music playing]
The case against me is dismissed.
I will be going back to the capitol
to claim my rightful title
as governor of Ardiente!
Suspiciously, why is Lily Cruz not here?
As a matter of fact,
she's leaving the country,
and my people are already after her.
[Emilia] Piece of advice.
Lily Cruz never flees.
And more importantly, she never dies.
[Helena] Lily, what are you doing here?
I am the one who will expose
the real identity of Helena Montoya.
[theme music playing]